<resources>
    <string name="app_name"></string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="title_activity_about_scrolling">AboutScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "About this App :\n\n"

        "Sparkle Code is an android application created by a collage student which contain series"
        "of question in order to get enough knowledge on programming in general and specially python language.\n"
        "sparkle Code is for the young children from 6 to 14 years old, every question works by re-arrange"
        "block of code in order to solve the problem ,The main goal of this learning method is to get more closer to the child. \n"
        "every question also contain text to clarify of what is the problem taking about?"
        "With 3 point for each question, this will courage the kid to solve it and get more and more point which will pased on "
        "a score and shows at the end of every level the kid finish. "
        "A simple log in that require only email with password will make the child knows how many points has been collected,
        each time the user arrange the code in wrong order it will show them an error message, if the user gets any hint,
        point counter will decrease automatically.\n\n"


        "About the Developer.\n"
        "This application considered as a graduation project,the developer is a student in Al-Nahrain University  \n\n "
        "email : shamsnaji4@gmail.com"

    </string>
    <string name="hint1_text">This is how we arrange the code, because in python the code will implemented
        line by line, and this also true in the print method</string>
    <string name="hint2_text">This is how we arrange the code in the right way because of the input  method,
        it will wait for an input from the user,and then the print method bring the output result to the screen</string>
    <string name="hint5_text">Settings</string>
    <string name="q8_output">12,"Hello",3.4</string>


    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="ooops_this_is_a_wrong_answer_and_might_cause_you_a_compiler_error">
        Ooops!! This is a wrong answer and Might Cause you a compiler error!</string>
    <string name="let_s_go_to_the_next_level">Let\'s go to the next level !</string>
    <string name="congratulation_you_passed_the_first_level_successfully">
        Congratulation!, You passed the First level successfully !</string>
    <string name="re_arrange_to_the_bottom_to_print_code_word">
        Re-Arrange to the bottom to print CODE word:</string>
    <string name="re_arrange_the_code_to_print_yes_if_x">
        Re-Arrange the code to print Yes, if x input is greater than y input:</string>
    <string name="q_2_of_3">Q 2 of 3</string>
    <string name="score">Score :</string>
    <string name="check_your_answer">Check your Answer</string>
    <string name="in_programming_an_array_is_a_collection_of_elements_of_the_same_type">
        In programming, an array is a collection of elements of the same type.
    to define any array in python :you need to import library called arr</string>
    <string name ="hint9">An array is a data structure that stores values of same data type.
        In Python, this is the main difference between arrays and lists.
        While python lists can contain values corresponding to different data types,
        arrays in python can only contain values corresponding to same data type.
        and here is how it work :</string>
    <string name ="hint5">If statement works here by comparing the two input, and it depends on what the user enter.\n and for more information,see help.</string>
    <string name="for_question">
        To loop through a set of code a specified number of times, we can use the range() function.
        The range() function returns a sequence of numbers, starting from 0 by default, and ends at a specified number</string>
    <string name="a_list_is_created">In Python programming, a list is created by placing all the items (elements)
        inside a square bracket [ ], separated by commas. It can have any number of items and they may be of different types
        (integer, float, string etc.).</string>
    <string name="else_explain">An else statement contains the block of code that executes if the conditional expression in the
        if statement resolves to 0 or a FALSE value. The else statement is an optional statement and there could be at most only one
        else statement following if.</string>
    <string name="for_x_in_range_1_6">for x in range(1,6):</string>
</resources>
